Open navigation menu [Open search](https://mezeaudio.com/search)

* HEADPHONES
    
    * Open-back
    * Closed-back
    * In-Ear
    * Limited edition
    
* STORE

* COMMUNITY

USD $

Country

 European Store (EUR €) International Store (USD $) Afghanistan (USD $) Algeria (USD $) Angola (USD $) Anguilla (USD $) Antigua & Barbuda (USD $) Argentina (USD $) Aruba (USD $) Australia (USD $) Azerbaijan (USD $) Bahamas (USD $) Bahrain (USD $) Bangladesh (USD $) Barbados (USD $) Belize (USD $) Benin (USD $) Bermuda (USD $) Bhutan (USD $) Bolivia (USD $) Botswana (USD $) Brazil (USD $) British Indian Ocean Territory (USD $) British Virgin Islands (USD $) Brunei (USD $) Burkina Faso (USD $) Burundi (USD $) Cambodia (USD $) Cameroon (USD $) Canada (USD $) Cape Verde (USD $) Cayman Islands (USD $) Central African Republic (USD $) Chad (USD $) Chile (USD $) China (USD $) Christmas Island (USD $) Cocos (Keeling) Islands (USD $) Colombia (USD $) Comoros (USD $) Congo - Brazzaville (USD $) Congo - Kinshasa (USD $) Cook Islands (USD $) Costa Rica (USD $) Côte d’Ivoire (USD $) Cuba (USD $) Curaçao (USD $) Djibouti (USD $) Dominica (USD $) Dominican Republic (USD $) Ecuador (USD $) Egypt (USD $) El Salvador (USD $) Equatorial Guinea (USD $) Eritrea (USD $) Eswatini (USD $) Ethiopia (USD $) Falkland Islands (USD $) Fiji (USD $) French Guiana (USD $) French Polynesia (USD $) Gabon (USD $) Gambia (USD $) Ghana (USD $) Grenada (USD $) Guatemala (USD $) Guinea (USD $) Guinea-Bissau (USD $) Guyana (USD $) Haiti (USD $) Honduras (USD $) Hong Kong SAR (USD $) India (USD $) Indonesia (USD $) Iraq (USD $) Israel (USD $) Jamaica (USD $) Jordan (USD $) Kazakhstan (USD $) Kenya (USD $) Kiribati (USD $) Kuwait (USD $) Kyrgyzstan (USD $) Laos (USD $) Lebanon (USD $) Lesotho (USD $) Liberia (USD $) Libya (USD $) Macao SAR (USD $) Madagascar (USD $) Malawi (USD $) Malaysia (USD $) Maldives (USD $) Mali (USD $) Martinique (USD $) Mauritania (USD $) Mauritius (USD $) Mayotte (USD $) Mexico (USD $) Mongolia (USD $) Montserrat (USD $) Morocco (USD $) Mozambique (USD $) Myanmar (Burma) (USD $) Namibia (USD $) Nauru (USD $) Nepal (USD $) Netherlands Antilles (USD $) New Caledonia (USD $) New Zealand (USD $) Nicaragua (USD $) Niger (USD $) Nigeria (USD $) Niue (USD $) Norfolk Island (USD $) Oman (USD $) Pakistan (USD $) Palestinian Territories (USD $) Panama (USD $) Papua New Guinea (USD $) Paraguay (USD $) Peru (USD $) Philippines (USD $) Pitcairn Islands (USD $) Qatar (USD $) Rwanda (USD $) Samoa (USD $) São Tomé & Príncipe (USD $) Saudi Arabia (USD $) Senegal (USD $) Seychelles (USD $) Sierra Leone (USD $) Singapore (USD $) Sint Maarten (USD $) Solomon Islands (USD $) Somalia (USD $) South Africa (USD $) South Korea (USD $) Sri Lanka (USD $) St. Barthélemy (USD $) St. Helena (USD $) St. Kitts & Nevis (USD $) St. Lucia (USD $) St. Martin (USD $) St. Pierre & Miquelon (USD $) St. Vincent & Grenadines (USD $) Sudan (USD $) Suriname (USD $) Svalbard & Jan Mayen (USD $) Taiwan (USD $) Tajikistan (USD $) Tanzania (USD $) Thailand (USD $) Timor-Leste (USD $) Togo (USD $) Tokelau (USD $) Tonga (USD $) Trinidad & Tobago (USD $) Tunisia (USD $) Turkmenistan (USD $) Turks & Caicos Islands (USD $) Tuvalu (USD $) U.S. Outlying Islands (USD $) Uganda (USD $) United Arab Emirates (USD $) United States (USD $) Uruguay (USD $) Uzbekistan (USD $) Vanuatu (USD $) Venezuela (USD $) Vietnam (USD $) Wallis & Futuna (USD $) Western Sahara (USD $) Yemen (USD $) Zambia (USD $) Zimbabwe (USD $)

[Open search](https://mezeaudio.com/search) [Open account page](https://mezeaudio.com/account) [Open cart

0](https://mezeaudio.com/cart)

* HEADPHONES
* STORE
* COMMUNITY

USD $

Country

 European Store (EUR €) International Store (USD $) Afghanistan (USD $) Algeria (USD $) Angola (USD $) Anguilla (USD $) Antigua & Barbuda (USD $) Argentina (USD $) Aruba (USD $) Australia (USD $) Azerbaijan (USD $) Bahamas (USD $) Bahrain (USD $) Bangladesh (USD $) Barbados (USD $) Belize (USD $) Benin (USD $) Bermuda (USD $) Bhutan (USD $) Bolivia (USD $) Botswana (USD $) Brazil (USD $) British Indian Ocean Territory (USD $) British Virgin Islands (USD $) Brunei (USD $) Burkina Faso (USD $) Burundi (USD $) Cambodia (USD $) Cameroon (USD $) Canada (USD $) Cape Verde (USD $) Cayman Islands (USD $) Central African Republic (USD $) Chad (USD $) Chile (USD $) China (USD $) Christmas Island (USD $) Cocos (Keeling) Islands (USD $) Colombia (USD $) Comoros (USD $) Congo - Brazzaville (USD $) Congo - Kinshasa (USD $) Cook Islands (USD $) Costa Rica (USD $) Côte d’Ivoire (USD $) Cuba (USD $) Curaçao (USD $) Djibouti (USD $) Dominica (USD $) Dominican Republic (USD $) Ecuador (USD $) Egypt (USD $) El Salvador (USD $) Equatorial Guinea (USD $) Eritrea (USD $) Eswatini (USD $) Ethiopia (USD $) Falkland Islands (USD $) Fiji (USD $) French Guiana (USD $) French Polynesia (USD $) Gabon (USD $) Gambia (USD $) Ghana (USD $) Grenada (USD $) Guatemala (USD $) Guinea (USD $) Guinea-Bissau (USD $) Guyana (USD $) Haiti (USD $) Honduras (USD $) Hong Kong SAR (USD $) India (USD $) Indonesia (USD $) Iraq (USD $) Israel (USD $) Jamaica (USD $) Jordan (USD $) Kazakhstan (USD $) Kenya (USD $) Kiribati (USD $) Kuwait (USD $) Kyrgyzstan (USD $) Laos (USD $) Lebanon (USD $) Lesotho (USD $) Liberia (USD $) Libya (USD $) Macao SAR (USD $) Madagascar (USD $) Malawi (USD $) Malaysia (USD $) Maldives (USD $) Mali (USD $) Martinique (USD $) Mauritania (USD $) Mauritius (USD $) Mayotte (USD $) Mexico (USD $) Mongolia (USD $) Montserrat (USD $) Morocco (USD $) Mozambique (USD $) Myanmar (Burma) (USD $) Namibia (USD $) Nauru (USD $) Nepal (USD $) Netherlands Antilles (USD $) New Caledonia (USD $) New Zealand (USD $) Nicaragua (USD $) Niger (USD $) Nigeria (USD $) Niue (USD $) Norfolk Island (USD $) Oman (USD $) Pakistan (USD $) Palestinian Territories (USD $) Panama (USD $) Papua New Guinea (USD $) Paraguay (USD $) Peru (USD $) Philippines (USD $) Pitcairn Islands (USD $) Qatar (USD $) Rwanda (USD $) Samoa (USD $) São Tomé & Príncipe (USD $) Saudi Arabia (USD $) Senegal (USD $) Seychelles (USD $) Sierra Leone (USD $) Singapore (USD $) Sint Maarten (USD $) Solomon Islands (USD $) Somalia (USD $) South Africa (USD $) South Korea (USD $) Sri Lanka (USD $) St. Barthélemy (USD $) St. Helena (USD $) St. Kitts & Nevis (USD $) St. Lucia (USD $) St. Martin (USD $) St. Pierre & Miquelon (USD $) St. Vincent & Grenadines (USD $) Sudan (USD $) Suriname (USD $) Svalbard & Jan Mayen (USD $) Taiwan (USD $) Tajikistan (USD $) Tanzania (USD $) Thailand (USD $) Timor-Leste (USD $) Togo (USD $) Tokelau (USD $) Tonga (USD $) Trinidad & Tobago (USD $) Tunisia (USD $) Turkmenistan (USD $) Turks & Caicos Islands (USD $) Tuvalu (USD $) U.S. Outlying Islands (USD $) Uganda (USD $) United Arab Emirates (USD $) United States (USD $) Uruguay (USD $) Uzbekistan (USD $) Vanuatu (USD $) Venezuela (USD $) Vietnam (USD $) Wallis & Futuna (USD $) Western Sahara (USD $) Yemen (USD $) Zambia (USD $) Zimbabwe (USD $)

* HEADPHONES
* Open-back
* Closed-back
* In-Ear
* Limited edition

* STORE

* COMMUNITY

* Open-back

* Closed-back

* In-Ear

* Limited edition

LIMITED TIME OFFER: 30% OFF 99 SERIES HEADPHONES FROM JULY 15TH TO 21ST

Close

Cookie policy

We use cookies and similar technologies to provide the best experience on our website. Refer to our Privacy Policy for more information.

Accept Decline

0

Your cart is empty

 Clear Close

Privacy Policy
==============

### 1\. Who we are

MEZE AUDIO SRL is a company registered in Romania responsible for producing, marketing and selling of Meze Audio products.

### 2\. What personal data do we process

MEZE AUDIO SRL is a personal data controller. We collect the following types of personal data from you:

* Name, surname
* Country
* Email
* Billing Information
* Delivery Address
* Invoice
* Client ID
* Transaction ID
* Purchase history
* Online activity

### 3\. Why do we need them

We need your personal data to provide you with the following services:

On the legal basis of controller’s legitimate interest to answer your messages from our contact form:

* Name, surname – we use this data to personalize your answer.
* Country – we use this data to help us better understand your issue and connect you to local dealers and distributors.
* Email – we use this data to answer your message.
* Subject, Order Number, Model Name, Audio Source, Message – we use this data to address your issues or questions.

On the legal basis of fulfilling our contractual obligations:

Creation of account, purchase, and delivery of products:

* Name, surname – we use this data to communicate with you and to process your orders.
* Email – we use this data to answer your email to communicate with you and to communicate your orders.
* Client ID – each user is assigned a Client ID on the platform that is used for processing transactions.
* Billing information – this information is required in order to issue an invoice for the products you are purchasing.
* Delivery Address – this is where we will be shipping the products you purchase.
* Invoice – since your name is on the invoice, this becomes personal data.
* Transaction ID – each transaction has a unique ID.

Based on our legitimate interest to offer you the best customer experience:

* Purchase history – here you can find a list of all your purchases.

With your consent, we would also like to make the following processing of personal data:

* Newsletter delivery

* Name, surname – we need this information to customize your newsletter.
* Email – we need this information to send you the newsletter.
* Country – we need this information to better understand your local needs.

* Online behavior

* Browsing History – We share this information with our partners described in our cookie policy so that we can deliver you personalized offers. More information found in our cookies page at [Cookie policy page](https://mezeaudio.com/pages/cookie-policy).

### 4\. What we do with them

Your personal data is processed within MEZE AUDIO SRL company located in Romania.

Hosting and storing of your data take place on Shopify platform, managed by Shopify Inc, a Canadian-based company, acting as Data Sub-Processor for Shopify International Limited, an Irish-based Data Processor for MEZE AUDIO SRL. The international personal data transfer compliance to Canada is guaranteed by the adequacy decision issued by the European Commission to Canadian companies.

Your personal data is also processed by Sendinblue SAS, a French-based company acting as Data Processor for MEZE AUDIO SRL, offering the Brevo platform for newsletter management.

Your personal data might also be processed by one of our payment partners (depending on how you choose to pay for the products you want to buy):

* Stripe, Inc – a US-based payment processor, acting as Data Controller, for credit and debit card payments. The international personal data transfer compliance to the United States is guaranteed by the adequacy decision issued by the European Commission to companies that are part of the Data Privacy Framework program.
* PayPal, Inc – a US-based payment processor, acting as Data Controller, for credit card, debit card, and Paypal payments. The international personal data transfer compliance to the United States is guaranteed by the adequacy decision issued by the European Commission to companies that are part of the Data Privacy Framework program.
* Klarna Bank AB – a Swedish-based bank and fintech which offers the Klarna payments platform, allowing you to split payments for the products you choose to buy.

Your personal data is also processed by Route App, Inc, a US-based company which acts as a Data Processor for MEZE AUDIO SRL, offering shipment management and insurance. The international personal data transfer compliance to the United States is guaranteed by the Standard Contractual Clauses signed by MEZE AUDIO SRL and Route App, Inc.

Your personal data is also processed by Cargo-Partner Headquarter GmbH, a German-based company acting as Data Controller, managing shipments and deliveries.

Your personal data is also processed by Amazon, Inc, a US-based company acting as Data Controller, managing shipments and deliveries. The international personal data transfer compliance to the United States is guaranteed by the adequacy decision issued by the European Commission to companies that are part of the Data Privacy Framework program.

Your personal data is also processed by Everflow Technologies Inc and ShareASale.com Inc, two US-based companies acting as Data Controllers, offering affiliate-based platforms allowing our affiliates to get paid for their activities. The international personal data transfer compliance to the United States is guaranteed by the Standard Contractual Clauses signed by MEZE AUDIO SRL and these companies.

Your personal data is also processed by different shipping companies, depending on your location, who act as Data Controllers.

Your personal data for browsing history is transmitted to our partners described in the cookies policy, which act as joint controllers.

### 5\. How long do we keep personal data

Your account data will be retained for three years since your last login on the platform under the legitimate interest of MEZE AUDIO SRL to maintain your account in case of inactivity.

Personal data that are contained in the financial-accounting documents or in documents that are attached to the financial-accounting documents (all data from your bookings are included), will be kept for 10 years according to the provisions of art. 38 of Annex 1 to Order no. 2634/2015 on financial-accounting documents, issued by the Ministry of Public Finance and will not be accessed for any purpose other than the legal purpose for which they are archived. After 10 years these data will be destroyed.

Personal data for the newsletter will be retained for five years or till you revoke your consent.

Personal data from cookies will be retained for the duration of the cookie or till you delete the cookie. For more information, please visit our [Cookie Policy page](https://mezeaudio.com/pages/cookie-policy).

### 6\. What are your rights?

If you have reason to believe that any personal data that we have about you is incorrect or incomplete, you have the right to ask to see your personal data, to correct it, to request to be deleted, to request restriction of processing or to object to the processing. You also have the right to data portability. To exercise these rights please contact us at support@mezeaudio.com.

For the newsletter, you have the right to withdraw your consent. You can do this by sending an email to support@mezeaudio.com or by unsubscribing directly from the newsletter.

If you want to file a complaint about how we process your personal data, please contact us at support@mezeaudio.com. We will contact you to solve the problem raised.

You can also contact the Romanian National Supervisory Authority for the processing of personal data at [www.dataprotection.ro](http://www.dataprotection.ro/) and you can file a complaint.

Social Media Privacy Notice
---------------------------

### 1\. Who we are

MEZE AUDIO SRL is a company registered in Romania responsible for producing, marketing and selling of Meze Audio products.

### 2\. What personal data do we process

MEZE AUDIO SRL is a personal data controller together with Facebook as Joint Controllers. Our relationship is based on a joint controller agreement which is available here:

[https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms/page\_controller\_addendum](https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms/page_controller_addendum)

We process the following types of personal data from you:

* Name and surname
* Facebook ID
* Phone number
* Delivery Address
* Post on Hotel Stil Page

For more details regarding the personal data processed by Facebook please visit [https://www.facebook.com/policy.php.](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)

### 3\. Why do we need them

We need your personal data to provide you with the following services:

On the legal basis of necessity to process personal data for the performance of a contract to which you are party (namely, the Terms and Conditions for a Contest or a Lucky Draw):

* Name and surname – we need this info to know who we are talking with.
* Facebook ID – we need this info to know who we are talking with.
* Phone number - we need this information to contact you.
* Delivery address - we need this information to be able to deliver your prize
* National Identification Number (CNP) – this information is collected for the payment of the tax on prizes over 600 lei, according to the fiscal code.
* Post on Meze Audio page – here you might add unsolicited personal data of other persons. The post must adhere to Facebook rules. For the personal data of other persons that might be in your post (name, images, etc) you are a data controller, and you are directly responsible to make sure you took all necessary technical and organizational measures to prove compliance to GDPR.

On the legal basis of controller’s legitimate interest to answer your posts on the Meze Audio Facebook page:

* Name and surname – we need this info to know who we are talking with.
* Facebook ID – we need this info to know who we are talking with.
* Post on Meze Audio Page – here you might add unsolicited personal data of other persons. The post must adhere to Facebook rules. For the personal data of other persons that might be in your post (name, images etc) you are a data controller and you are directly responsible to make sure you took all necessary technical and organizational measures to prove compliance to GDPR.

### 5\. How long do we keep personal data

Personal data from your posts or evaluations on Meze Audio page will be kept till you decide to delete your post or till you ask us to delete your personal data.

Your personal data from the competitions will be kept for 3 months from the end of the contests, unless you are a winner. If you are a winner we will keep your personal data for five years as required by the fiscal code and if you win a prize which has a value of over 600 lei we will keep your personal data for 10 year as required by the fiscal code.

As a Data Controller Facebook has its own data retention policy which can be consulted here: [https://www.facebook.com/policy.php.](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)

### 6\. What are your rights?

If you have reasons to believe that any personal data that we have about you is incorrect or incomplete you have the right to ask to see your personal data, to correct it, to request to be deleted, to request restriction of processing or to object to the processing. You also have the right to data portability. To exercise these rights please contact us at [support@mezeaudio.com](mailto:support@mezeaudio.com)

If you want to file a complaint about how we process your personal data please contact us at [support@mezeaudio.com](mailto:support@mezeaudio.com). We will contact you to solve the problem raised.

In order to exercise your privacy rights with Facebook please check their privacy policy: [https://www.facebook.com/policy.php](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)

You can also contact the Romanian Data Protection Authority at [www.dataprotection.ro](https://www.dataprotection.ro/) in order to file a complaint.

Go to item 1 Go to item 2 Go to item 3

ABOUT US

OUR WORLD

CUSTOMER CARE

**TUNE IN WITH THE WORLDWIDE AUDIO COMMUNITY**

The realm of superior sound awaits you. Delight in personalised content, including product updates, exclusive rewards and events, and much more, delivered directly to your inbox.

E-mail

Subscribe

Apple Pay Google Pay PayPal  [ Klarna](https://mezeaudio.com/pages/about-klarna)

© 2024, Meze Audio - Sound. Comfort. Design. True high-end.
